{
  "id": 1,
  "name": "Byron Monahan",
  "email": "Louie_Franey@hotmail.com",
  "password": "ACYxpWB298M9Gqz",
  "phone_number": "010-2405-7320",
  "address": "515 Kub Prairie",
  "resident_number_front": "762446",
  "resident_number_back": "1",
  "point": "8723651",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:38:13",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 2,
  "name": "Miss Alvin Jaskolski",
  "email": "Johann1@hotmail.com",
  "password": "coQQ066IkVHQ4sG",
  "phone_number": "010-2175-6592",
  "address": "39983 Elias Mountains",
  "resident_number_front": "112144",
  "resident_number_back": "3",
  "point": "7506793",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:38:13",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 3,
  "name": "Donnie Ward",
  "email": "Ona.Lesch@hotmail.com",
  "password": "YXf_gP62inuHRgA",
  "phone_number": "010-3647-1927",
  "address": "362 Hyatt Walk",
  "resident_number_front": "701790",
  "resident_number_back": "1",
  "point": "9222980",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:38:13",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 4,
  "name": "Cindy Donnelly",
  "email": "Shany6@hotmail.com",
  "password": "mYmeiriebv6ID5T",
  "phone_number": "010-5331-2522",
  "address": "827 Kub Fords",
  "resident_number_front": "124394",
  "resident_number_back": "4",
  "point": "8134882",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:39:47",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 5,
  "name": "Mr. Kevin Cronin",
  "email": "Kaci_Bergnaum@yahoo.com",
  "password": "JbzeO31WHpyuyhM",
  "phone_number": "010-0156-3667",
  "address": "83987 Ritchie Lodge",
  "resident_number_front": "476555",
  "resident_number_back": "4",
  "point": "6939337",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:39:47",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 6,
  "name": "Cindy Lakin",
  "email": "Bulah.Sporer85@gmail.com",
  "password": "kTJNedDegzBfuOx",
  "phone_number": "010-8912-1709",
  "address": "06144 Connelly Gardens",
  "resident_number_front": "743680",
  "resident_number_back": "2",
  "point": "2953499",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:39:47",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 7,
  "name": "Jill Schoen",
  "email": "Hilbert.Rogahn80@yahoo.com",
  "password": "2bHCvGREqQNtWbR",
  "phone_number": "010-7950-7133",
  "address": "8752 Frami Station",
  "resident_number_front": "491134",
  "resident_number_back": "2",
  "point": "6673763",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 8,
  "name": "Martha Stamm",
  "email": "Kamren.Nienow27@gmail.com",
  "password": "Bvyi13_8hsXDUNs",
  "phone_number": "010-7914-3659",
  "address": "402 Rolfson Estate",
  "resident_number_front": "272003",
  "resident_number_back": "2",
  "point": "6996614",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 9,
  "name": "Harriet Kilback",
  "email": "Ole72@yahoo.com",
  "password": "M1thNdrZHZ_yWPH",
  "phone_number": "010-1175-6627",
  "address": "40247 Romaguera Cliff",
  "resident_number_front": "376745",
  "resident_number_back": "2",
  "point": "1741197",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 10,
  "name": "Benny Gulgowski",
  "email": "Stefan.Kunze@gmail.com",
  "password": "xwx6rrNSJqjUGQv",
  "phone_number": "010-3561-3757",
  "address": "685 Anastacio Junction",
  "resident_number_front": "205769",
  "resident_number_back": "4",
  "point": "6754169",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 11,
  "name": "Matthew Schiller",
  "email": "Jolie65@hotmail.com",
  "password": "9fsCHTQNh2LuxFl",
  "phone_number": "010-9785-3839",
  "address": "40553 Lockman Mission",
  "resident_number_front": "342773",
  "resident_number_back": "2",
  "point": "1577965",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 12,
  "name": "Clifford Kessler",
  "email": "Hipolito54@hotmail.com",
  "password": "DMI2NlHzh0vtLzP",
  "phone_number": "010-1897-6113",
  "address": "424 Mackenzie Inlet",
  "resident_number_front": "799007",
  "resident_number_back": "1",
  "point": "8395336",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 13,
  "name": "Kurt Luettgen",
  "email": "Syble_Kerluke48@yahoo.com",
  "password": "cqRbcHMoDr2Y5yN",
  "phone_number": "010-8476-3803",
  "address": "4669 Haley Islands",
  "resident_number_front": "879267",
  "resident_number_back": "4",
  "point": "9124699",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 14,
  "name": "Wendell Adams",
  "email": "Esteban.Bartoletti@yahoo.com",
  "password": "rq1mEna7yN8GCWu",
  "phone_number": "010-0630-2714",
  "address": "293 Considine Lane",
  "resident_number_front": "154825",
  "resident_number_back": "2",
  "point": "6134744",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 15,
  "name": "Christie Bode",
  "email": "Dagmar84@yahoo.com",
  "password": "8ykUbLuqn3Uxszs",
  "phone_number": "010-7574-2411",
  "address": "24827 Sonny Union",
  "resident_number_front": "739096",
  "resident_number_back": "1",
  "point": "4065212",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 16,
  "name": "Della Prohaska V",
  "email": "Ike59@hotmail.com",
  "password": "nvee_tetfZop2by",
  "phone_number": "010-6736-9533",
  "address": "215 Collins Hollow",
  "resident_number_front": "889552",
  "resident_number_back": "3",
  "point": "7671343",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 17,
  "name": "Mike Flatley PhD",
  "email": "Chad77@hotmail.com",
  "password": "RDOlUUG0Hi6lJFL",
  "phone_number": "010-5357-5263",
  "address": "454 Marion Summit",
  "resident_number_front": "245795",
  "resident_number_back": "1",
  "point": "9519462",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 18,
  "name": "Kerry Maggio",
  "email": "Jada_Champlin@gmail.com",
  "password": "n7lGclfoas5341B",
  "phone_number": "010-5172-3699",
  "address": "0042 Goldner Motorway",
  "resident_number_front": "172029",
  "resident_number_back": "4",
  "point": "1644405",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 19,
  "name": "Clyde Bergnaum",
  "email": "Madisen_Sporer@yahoo.com",
  "password": "I5aUEGSKMOtxz2G",
  "phone_number": "010-5801-4908",
  "address": "476 Domenico Hills",
  "resident_number_front": "724354",
  "resident_number_back": "3",
  "point": "7009106",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 20,
  "name": "Matthew Fisher",
  "email": "Elbert_Cartwright96@hotmail.com",
  "password": "oMSEMy2HoXeg1a_",
  "phone_number": "010-7544-1865",
  "address": "847 Dibbert Mews",
  "resident_number_front": "822332",
  "resident_number_back": "4",
  "point": "4149169",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 21,
  "name": "Santiago Okuneva DVM",
  "email": "Marilyne_Purdy37@yahoo.com",
  "password": "iXvkDvsnWRkLQkL",
  "phone_number": "010-6497-3011",
  "address": "81936 Ella Route",
  "resident_number_front": "780812",
  "resident_number_back": "3",
  "point": "2485809",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
},
{
  "id": 22,
  "name": "Franklin Dach",
  "email": "Monserrat56@hotmail.com",
  "password": "xjnOuJLRYy7p0q4",
  "phone_number": "010-4960-5361",
  "address": "3779 Beer Groves",
  "resident_number_front": "642885",
  "resident_number_back": "4",
  "point": "3943619",
  "created_at": "2022-10-18 18:40:33",
  "updated_at": null
}